(Raj:)In the last two hours,
162 women have read our profiles.
(Raj:)How many of them
have sent us messages?
(Stuart:)-Combined?
-Yes.
(Stuart:)Zero.
(Raj:)Dude, this is... this is brutal.
(Stuart:)I don't think I've ever felt
so rejected.
(Stuart:)And I had a rescue dog
who ran back to the pound.
(Raj:)This is the worst.
(Raj:)If we're gonna get shot down,
(Raj:)we might as well just go to a bar
and do it old-school.
(Stuart:)-And make them look us in the eye.
-Yeah, anything is better than this.
(Amy(on webcam):)-Hello.
-Not interested.
I (POP MUSIC PLAYS) I
(Raj:)I was wrong. This is worse.
I (INDIANA JONES THEME PLAYS) I
(Howard:)Wait, wait.
If it wasn't for Indiana Jones,
(Howard:)the ark would never have ended up
at the warehouse!
That's true!
(Sheldon:)He collected and delivered the ark
to the proper authorities for filing.
-Like a hero!
-Yes!
(Leonard:)Although, technically,
Indy was supposed to take the ark
(Leonard:)to a museum to be studied.
He couldn't even get that done.
(ALL GRUMBLE)